{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","address":"19041 Van Dyke Ave","zipcode":"48234","owner":"Mahdiur Rahman","licenseNumber":"067904","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/21/2016","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180.0","geom":"0101000020E61000004C48125492C154C0B82F5FB27F374540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44717","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2019-01-03T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44717","inspectionDate":"1/3/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"44717","inspectionDate":"1/3/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Above the","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-01-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44717","inspectionDate":"1/3/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair"},{"inspectionid":"44717","inspectionDate":"1/3/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FREEZER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"44717","inspectionDate":"1/3/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"6-201.17","violationDescription":"(A) Except as otherwise allowed by law, attachments to walls and ceilings such as light fixtures, mechanical room ventilation system components, vent covers, wall mounted fans, decorative items, and other attachments shall be EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) In a CONSUMER area, wall and ceiling surfaces and decorative items and attachments that are provided for ambiance need not meet this requirement if they are kept clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Wall attachment(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"44717","inspectionDate":"1/3/2019","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Nonfood contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"THROUGHOUT FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"42685","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"1","pfcount":"1","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"42685","inspectionDate":"6/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"inspectionid":"42685","inspectionDate":"6/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"inspectionid":"42685","inspectionDate":"6/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-501.13","violationDescription":"POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be thawed:  Under refrigeration, or under cool running water (<70° F), or as part of cooking process, and total accumulated time above 41° F, for thawed portions, shall not exceed 4 hours.  Any thawing procedure may be used for immediate service for individual consumers order of READY-TO-EAT foods.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Frozen food(s) for thawing","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F thawed or partially thawed","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-06-28T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store under refrigeration."},{"inspectionid":"42685","inspectionDate":"6/28/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"4-602.13","violationDescription":"NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be cleaned at a frequency necessary to preclude accumulation of soil residues.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN COOLER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"41073","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2017-12-11T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"41148","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"2","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"41148","inspectionDate":"12/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"7-201.11","violationDescription":"POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL shall be stored so they can not contaminate FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES by:   \r\n(A) Separating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL by spacing or partitioning; (P) and   \r\n(B) Locating the POISONOUS OR TOXIC MATERIAL in an area that is not above FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE AND SINGLE-USE ARTICLES.  This paragraph does not apply to EQUIPMENT and UTENSIL cleaners and sanitizers that are stored in WAREWASHING areas for availability and convenience if the materials are stored to prevent contamination of FOOD, EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, LINENS, AND SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES. (P)","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Poisonous/toxic material(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not separated from","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Relocate."},{"inspectionid":"41148","inspectionDate":"12/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-302.12","violationDescription":"Except for containers holding FOOD that can be readily and unmistakably recognized such as dry pasta, working containers holding FOOD or FOOD ingredients that are removed from their original packages for use in the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, such as cooking oils, flour, herbs, potato flakes, salt, spices, and sugar shall be identified with the common name of the FOOD.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not identified","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE AREA(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Label containers with common name."},{"inspectionid":"41148","inspectionDate":"12/5/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"GRILL AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-12-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store above 135 degrees F."}]},{"inspectionid":"39297","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2017-06-14T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"39297","inspectionDate":"6/14/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"39297","inspectionDate":"6/14/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"inspectionid":"39297","inspectionDate":"6/14/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Hot food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored below 135 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COUNTER","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-06-14T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard"}]},{"inspectionid":"37143","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","inspectionDate":"2016-11-17T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"126","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"37143","inspectionDate":"11/17/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"3620","name":"Captain Jay's Fish & Chicken","violationCode":"3-305.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be protected from contamination by storing the FOOD:\r\n(1)     In a clean, dry location;\r\n(2)     Where it is not exposed to splash, dust, or other contamination; and\r\n(3)     At least 15 cm (6 inches) above the floor, unless otherwise approved.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food item(s) in storage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Exposed to dust, splash, or other contaminates","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store in manner that does not contaminate items"}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"3620"}}